Staying on theme of horrible drivers making terrible decisions yesterday
I talked about the lady who wouldn't stop texting and driving and then crash the rented vehicle
Today I want to talk about Jeffrey the boy wonder who won't stop drinking and driving
Did you just get into an accident? No, I need to stay here. Nope, you can't go back in your car right now
Because it's not safe for you to go in your car. Nope, take it in your car. Nope
Thank you. Oh, I can't. No, you can't. You're just gonna have to go.
When I saw this Midwest safety clip for the first like two seconds
I thought for a second that it was Yokech. I thought he went from buckets to brusquies here. It turns out it is a
Gentlesur named Jeffrey and the way he is holding that case of beer
It's like a like a precious artifact to him
He's holding it like a running back holds a football now Jeffrey's already been in one accident here
His car is smoking and now he's got a brand new case of beer because he's ready to really get this fart
He's sharded and he very much already seems slushed and in officers like don't get into the car Jeffrey
You've been in an accident. You can't do that. He's like, no, I'm good. I'm getting in the car
You can't stop me. There's my beer and there's my car
You do the math
Get out of your car
The suspect is able to turn the officer's body camera off when the officer is able to reactivate her body camera
The suspect has violently backed up and then takes off prompting the officer to initiate a pursuit
I don't know if this was a calculated move from Jeffrey here
Maybe he's a high-tech hacker and just went into the mainframe here scrubbing the body camera footage getting rid of the evidence
Or if he was just like fighting back and just started like
poking at the body camera and happened to turn it off but regardless the footage is gone from the archives here and he was able to
Punch it in reverse and then just peel out so then it was time for a moderate speed pursuit
Just one minute before this interaction another officer in the area is interviewing the victim whose vehicle was hit by the same suspect just minutes earlier
There's three shot field I'm gonna stand back block traffic slow speeds 30 miles an hour
One of the units
Most of this chase happens at approximately 30 miles per hour
So my little game theory here is that he activated cruise control and just started fucking pounding those voodoo
Rangers in the passenger seat his man was probably butt chugging as much as he could knowing full well
This was probably the last time he'd have the chance to do that for a while
Possibly point 19 speeds are 32
Oh
Power caught off a big sigh from the officer here
So you can see Jeffery's not exactly staying in the in the lane
He is swerving all over the place dreadfully the man is
Hammered and he is only continuing to get more and more knee-breated
Because you'll see here towards the end he is actively drinking during the chase
Like I don't even think he recognizes that he's being chased
I really think in his world he's right now in like the fucking battle bus partying
Speed's 32 coming up the
Ancho
He's all over the road definitely point 19 that's
He comes dangerously close to head-on collisions with cars multiple times
I can only imagine what it was like to see this unfolding as you're just like driving home at night
And there's this fucking lunatic just going like this with the steering wheel coming right at you
That must be terrifying also I tell you what those mailbox must have been sweat and see in this douche bag coming through
The amount of times he gets close to kissing those mailboxes is astounding
He is like right next to them shaving them with his car so many times on this chase here still northbound
Pass of hemlocks feature 30
All right, he's getting on going the wrong way on
90 here going the wrong way
After a slow stroll around the area taking us on a bit of a tour
He finally decides to just go the wrong way on the highway and that's when the officers decide
We've got to do something about this now it's even more dangerous. So now they're readying the pit maneuver
I
There's some bump in and grinding they do get them to drive into a ditch
I guess it's not really a pit maneuver
They're looking more just to like bump them off the road to get them away from the cars
It seems and get like a I don't know maybe like box them in or something because they didn't really go for like the big-time pit maneuver
Where they swing out wine fucking blast the butt cheeks on the car anything it was more so like they were almost kind of like
shielding the road from this car like trying to just like grind them off to the side which eventually does work
Stand up
I can't why not stand up
Slim Shady goes on about how he can't stand up here after they've tased him so he
crashes his car into the ditch and then he immediately tries to run through the forest there
He does not get far. I don't think he knows where he is
So this man was probably just like running into like a tree like an NPC stuck on a wall
He actually only made it like maybe a foot or two despite bailing out of his car pretty early
Okay, so I said you're driving you go down the ditch
No bro, no, you guys are nothing we don't know
I live in America. I live in America. So do we yeah, right? So do we I live in America. I got stopped drinking just no
I live in America just as you do you guys just as you do what if I leave this
For safety country
That's a good best of luck to you
Now that was hard from Jeffrey right there. I live in America. What if I left this country, huh?
I don't know what he's expecting the response to be like no wait Jeff. Don't make that threat don't leave
America needs you Jeff you're a hero
You're the real patriot, but no Jeff. You can't leave don't don't say things are gonna regret
We can't lose you Jeff. Who's gonna drink all our voodoo Rangers? I recognize Jeffery is completely gone right now
But I find it fascinating how common this dialogue option is with drunk drivers
I've seen this exact statement from so many other drunk drivers in these body cams and shit where they all go like
I live in America. I'm an American god damn it. You're infringing on my rights
Wait, I thought this was a free country since when can I not drink beer while driving the wrong way on the highway
What's god what wait this country's gone to the birds. This is ridiculous
Hey
An officer finds open alcohol cans in the suspects vehicle
That's you open voodoo Rangers
This happens to be the exact same brand of beer the suspect was holding a case of at the beginning of this incident
Indicating he was likely drinking multiple cans of beer during the vehicle pursuit in the ambulance
He kept like lunging forward as if he was trying to jump scare officers or something like it was five nights at Freddy's
And then eventually they concluded with like a little high five. He's like okay. I five
Give me some skin
So anyway, they find some open voodoo Rangers in his car
Which is the same case he had in the very beginning of the video
I think we've got some real strong evidence to prove that he was
Probably drunk driving here. I would say I think that one's kind of locked in
He's been charged with quite a few things. I don't think he's been sentenced to anything yet
But uh yeah jeffery not good man
Be a good frown for me on this one brother drunk driving little PSA don't do it not good
That's about it. See ya